/*quiz_data3 */

const questions = [
    {
//306問目
question:"story(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["心配する","開発","接触","物語"],
correctAnswer: "物語"
    },
    {
//316問目
question:"sort(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["速度、率","一部","住所","現れる"],
correctAnswer: "一部"
    },
    {
//322問目
question:"water(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["水","日付","言及する","瞬間"],
correctAnswer: "水"
    },
    {
//325問目
question:"soon(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["主要な","すぐに","フィルム","フィルム"],
correctAnswer: "すぐに"
    },
    {
//341問目
question:"mind(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["顧慮する","心","機会","利用できる"],
correctAnswer: "心"
    },
    {
//349問目
question:"light(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["よい","特に","光、明かり","関係"],
correctAnswer: "光、明かり"
    },
    {
 //354問目
question:"real(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["個人の","文化","父親","本当の"],
correctAnswer: "本当の"
    },
    {
//357問目
question:"figure(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["食べ物","～しそうだ","図","色"],
correctAnswer: "図"
    },
    {
//363問目
question:"development(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["開発","警備","社会","メモ"],
correctAnswer: "開発"
    },
    {
//368問目
question:"break(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["壊す","従って、だから","選択","すぐに"],
correctAnswer: "壊す"
    }
];

export default questions;

